Devinder Narula

1349 Scotts Creek Circle, Mount Pleasant, SC 29464 410.533.8096 | devin.j.narula@gmail.com

Technical Skills

I have five years of experience with programming which consisted of java throughout high school, and c and c++ at the college level. Through this, I have good knowledge of object-oriented programming as well as various data structures and their implementations.

Experience

Blackbaud Inc. / Temporary Software Engineer

April 2018-August 2018, Charleston, SC

I conducted unit testing for the company in c# as well as researched app monitoring with Microsoft Azure. My main role at the company was testing code to ensure efficiency while gaining experience by learning about the other projects the team was working on.

Clemson University Honors College / Researcher

June 2019 - August 2019, Clemson, SC

I worked on a swarm robotics research project in the electrical engineering department as a part of the 2019 EUREKA! summer research program. I created an algorithm to localize a robot using sound and assisted in coding the algorithm.

Education

Clemson University Honors College

August 2019 - Present, Clemson, SC

Pursuing Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science with a minor in Mathematical Sciences.

Campus Involvement

Clemson University Undergraduate Student Government

September 2019 - Present, Clemson, SC

Freshman Council | September 2019 - Present, Clemson, SC

The role is a place for freshmen to serve in Clemson student government which often leads to future leadership roles at the university. I am on the community service committee where we organize and run service projects on campus.

Senate | December 2019 – March 2020, Clemson, SC

I served as a senator for four months on the innovation and technology committee. My primary roles were to vote on legislation and create a project which would allow more access to charging technologies for computers and phones on campus. I am currently continuing this project as a part of ITSAB.

Information Technology Student Advisory Board (ITSAB) | February 2020 - Present, Clemson, SC

ITSAB is a board where a group of students are given the opportunity to work with administrators and CCIT executives regarding IT related issues as well as allocate funding for technology related projects. My role was to advise the IT trajectory of the university from a student perspective as well as to aide in the allocation of this funding.

Projects and Github

Clemson Canvas Alexa Skill

I created this skill for an Amazon Alexa with a team of three others. It can access Canvas, the service Clemson uses for assignments, to read the user their upcoming assignments. It won best hardware hack in the 2019 HelloWorld Hackathon event at Clemson University.

Puddle iOS Application

This application was created in a team with three others. It functions as a pedestrian map application to alert people of obstacles in the area such as puddles. My role was to create the interface of the app while the other group members worked on the backend configurations. It won best use of Radar.io in the 2019 CUhackit hackathon event at Clemson University.

Github Link

https://github.com/devinnarula